Guide to Records of the Office of the President (John Brademas) RG.3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series XIII. Speeches and Writings, 1981-1991; 22.50 Linear Feet in 54 manuscript boxes.; 1 audiocassette; 3 VHS
  - Education Daily Consensus Panel Article, 1988-05 (Box 288, Folder 12)
  - University of Charleston Commencement Address (Charleston, WV), 1988-05-01 (Box 288, Folder 13)
  - Remarks on the Value of Public Service, the New York Federal Executive Board (New York, NY), 1988-05-02 (Box 288, Folder 14)
  - Tribute to Judge Edward Weinfeld (NYU), 1988-05-02 (Box 288, Folder 15)
  - Remarks on the Politics of Education, Seminar on Higher Education (NYU), 2 May 1988 (Box 288, Folder 16)
  - Real Estate Institute Breakfast (NYU), 1988-05-03 (Box 288, Folder 17)
  - Ceremony Presenting the School of Education, Health, Nursing, and the Arts Professions Prism Award (New York, NY), 1988-05-03 (Box 288, Folder 18)
  - Institute of Fine Art Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1988-05-04 (Box 102, Folder 18)
  - Casa Italiana Zerilli-Marimo Announcement Events (NYU), 1988-05-09 (Box 288, Folder 19)
  - NYU Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1988-05-09 (Box 102, Folder 19)
  - King Juan Carlos I Lecture Talking Points (NYU), 1988-05-11 (Box 288, Folder 20)
  - Urban Research Center for Visiting Mayors (NYU), 1988-05-12 (Box 288, Folder 21)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1988-05-12 (Box 288, Folder 22)
  - Sweeney Scholarship Program Luncheon (NYU), 1988-05-16 (Box 288, Folder 23)
  - 25-Year Service Awards Reception (NYU), 1988-05-17 (Box 288, Folder 24)
  - Dutch Treat Club Lunch (New York, NY), 1988-05-17 (Box 288, Folder 25)
  - Alumni Council Dinner (NYU), 1988-05-17 (Box 288, Folder 26)
  - French Bicentennial Program Luncheon (New York, NY), 1988-05-18 (Box 288, Folder 27)
  - CREO Society Concert and Dinner Talking Points (NYU), 1988-05-18 (Box 288, Folder 28)
  - NYU Community Fund Talking Points (NYU), 1988-05-19 (Box 288, Folder 29)
  - Virginia Commonwealth University Commencement Address (Richmond, VA), 1988-05-21 (Box 288, Folder 30)
  - South Bend Boosters Hall of Fame Banquet (South Bend, IN), 1988-05-21 (Box 288, Folder 31)
  - Fairleigh Dickinson University Commencement Remarks (East Rutherford, New Jersey), 1988-05-22 (Box 288, Folder 32)
  - Farewell to Dean Norman Redlich (New York, NY), 1988-05-31 (Box 288, Folder 33)
  - Introduction to the Benaki Museum Travelling Exhibition Catalog, 1988-06 (Box 288, Folder 34)
  - Luncheon Honoring Guggenheim Fellows (NYU), 1988-06-01 (Box 288, Folder 35)
  - Remarks and Script for Laurence Tisch, NYU Commencement Events (NYU), 1988-06-02-1988-06-03 (Box 288, Folder 36)
  - Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner (NYU), 1988-06-02 (Box 288, Folder 37)
  - 156th NYU Commencement, 1988-06-03 (Box 288, Folder 38)
  - Medical Center Board Meeting (RESTRICTED), 1988-06-10 (Box 102, Folder 288)
  - Reception for Dean Howard Newman (NYU), 1988-06-15 (Box 288, Folder 39)
  - Award Acceptance from the Greek Orthodox Archdiocese of North and South America (Boston, MA), 1988-07-06 (Box 288, Folder 40)
  - Education Daily Consensus Panel on College Athletics, 1988-07-07 (Box 288, Folder 41)
  - Reception for Washington Workshops (NYU), 1988-07-10 (Box 288, Folder 42)
  - Blurb for The Vulnerable Book, 1988-07-13 (Box 288, Folder 43)
  - Blurb for Merck & Co. Brochure, 1988-07-13 (Box 288, Folder 44)
  - Introduction of Mario Cuomo and Michael Dukakis (NYU), 1988-08-11 (Box 288, Folder 45)
  - Introduction of Michael Dukakis, National Security Policy Address (NYU), 1988-08-11 (Box 101, Video 32)
  - Metro Center Upward Bound Luncheon and Graduation (NYU), 1988-08-12 (Box 288, Folder 46)
  - NEXUS Article on Science, 1988-08-12 (Box 288, Folder 47)
  - Program Note for How to Succeed in Business Without Really Trying, NYU Summer Musical Theater Program, 1988-08-14 (Box 288, Folder 48)
  - Notes on Leadership, 1988-08-14 (Box 289, Folder 1)
  - Bronx Higher Education Breakfast (Bronx, NY), 1988-08-23 (Box 289, Folder 2)
  - Letter to Dr. Janet Kerr-Tener on Education Policy, 1988-08-25 (Box 289, Folder 3)
  - Comments on Draft Paper "Mike Dukakis on the Issues: College Opportunity", 1988-08-25 (Box 289, Folder 4)
  - NYU Magazine, Letter from the President, 1988-08-30 (Box 289, Folder 5)
  - Dedication of Sidney and Sarah Brown Study Center, Vanderbilt Hall (NYU), 1988-08-30 (Box 289, Folder 6)
  - School of Law Faculty Luncheon (NYU), 1988-09-01 (Box 289, Folder 7)
  - Foreword for The Presidency in American Politics, 1988-09-01 (Box 289, Folder 8)
  - Student Convocation (NYU), 1988-09-06 (Box 289, Folder 9)
  - Statement in Support of Micheal Dukakis, 1988-09-07 (Box 289, Folder 10)
  - New York State Board of Regents Meeting Talking Points, 1988-09-08 (Box 289, Folder 11)
  - Comments on Jill Krementz's Manuscript, 1988-09-12 (Box 289, Folder 12)
  - Comments on Dr. William Stratigos' Document, 1988-09-12 (Box 289, Folder 13)
  - Liberal Education Essay, 1988-09-14 (Box 289, Folder 14)
  - Letter to Harold Brown on "Congress and Foreign Policy" Paper, 1988-09-19 (Box 289, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting (NYU) RESTRICTED, 1988-09-19 (Box 102, Folder 20)
  - Response to George Bull Memo, 1988-09-20 (Box 289, Folder 16)
  - Harold Weill Medal Presentation Dinner (NYU), 1988-09-26 (Box 289, Folder 17)
  - Reception for New Graduate Students (NYU), 1988-09-27 (Box 289, Folder 18)
  - Remarks by Brademas and Laurence Tisch, Convocation and Dinner Honoring François Mitterrand (NYU), 1988-09-28 (Box 289, Folder 19)
  - Women's Campaign Fund Dinner (New York, NY), 1988-09-29 (Box 289, Folder 20)
  - Briefing for Rhodes Scholar Reunion, 1988-09-30 (Box 289, Folder 21)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration Conference on Japan-U.S. Relations (NYU), 1988-10-03 (Box 289, Folder 22)
  - "Education and The Nation's Agenda: Perspectives in an Election Year," Beta Gamma Sigma Alumni Dinner (NYU), 1988-10-03 (Box 289, Folder 23)
  - Charles Waldo Haskins Dinner (New York, NY), 1988-10-04 (Box 289, Folder 24)
  - Leonard N. Stern School of Business Press Conference (NYU), 1988-10-06 (Box 289, Folder 25)
  - American Council for the Arts Conference (New Brunswick, NJ), 1988-10-07 (Box 289, Folder 26)
  - Medical Center Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1988-10-07 (Box 102, Folder 22)
  - Celebration and Dinner Honoring Ioannis Georgakis and Speros Vryonis, Jr. (NYU), 1988-10-10 (Box 289, Folder 27)
  - Stern School of Business Board of Overseers Dinner (NYU), 1988-10-18 (Box 289, Folder 28)
  - Reception for Martin Luther King Scholars (NYU), 1988-10-20 (Box 289, Folder 29)
  - Art and Business Council Luncheon (New York, NY), 1988-10-20 (Box 289, Folder 30)
  - All-University Convocation (NYU), 1988-10-20 (Box 289, Folder 31)
  - Annual Archbishop Iakovos Feast Day Dinner (Washington, D.C.), 1988-10-22 (Box 289, Folder 32)
  - Dinner Honoring Graduate School of Public Administration Dean Howard Newman (NYU), 1988-10-24 (Box 289, Folder 33)
  - Campaign for Oxford Convocation (Oxford, England), 1988-10-26 (Box 289, Folder 34)
  - Allan Bloom Rebuttal Editorial, 1988-10-28 (Box 289, Folder 35)
  - "Education for a Strong and Secure America: An Election-Eve Perspective," the Woman's National Democratic Club (Washington, D.C.), 1988-10-31 (Box 289, Folder 36)
  - Memo Re: Post-Election Thoughts on the New President and Education, 1988-11-08 (Box 289, Folder 37)
  - Interview with The Chronicle of Higher Education, 1988-11-08 (Box 289, Folder 38)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1988-11-10 (Box 289, Folder 39)
  - NYU Opportunity Fellows Reception (NYU), 1988-11-14 (Box 289, Folder 40)
  - Bobst Awards in Arts and Letters (NYU), 1988-11-14 (Box 289, Folder 41)
  - "First Liberty" Forum Luncheon of the Williamsburg Charter Foundation, 1988-11-15 (Box 289, Folder 42)
  - Education Daily Consensus Panel on SATs, 1988-11-15 (Box 289, Folder 43)
  - Trustees Scholars Dinner (NYU), 1988-11-16 (Box 289, Folder 44)
  - Los Angeles Alumni Reception (Beverly Hills, CA), 1988-11-21 (Box 290, Folder 1)
  - Brademas Receives 1988 Axios Man of the Year Award (Beverly Hills, CA), 1988-11-22 (Box 290, Folder 2)
  - Economic Development Institute of the World Bank Seminar on Quality and Efficiency of Higher Education (Brasilia, Brazil), 1988-11-27 (Box 290, Folder 3)
  - "The Vision of Hubert Humphrey: Education for a Better Tomorrow," 10th Anniversary Hubert H. Humphrey North-South Fellowship Program (Rio de Janeiro, Brazil), 1988-12-01 (Box 290, Folder 4)
  - "The Vision of Hubert Humphrey: Education for a Better Tomorrow," 10th Anniversary Hubert H. Humphrey North-South Fellowship Program (Rio de Janeiro, Brazil), 1988-12-01 (Box 101, Video 36)
  - Reception for the Book: America in Theory (NYU), 1988-12-05 (Box 290, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Service Reception (NYU), 1988-12-05, 1988-12-07 (Box 290, Folder 6)
  - Medical Center Board Executive Committee Meeting RESTRICTED, 1988-12-06 (Box 102, Folder 23)
  - Introduction of Congressman Dan Rostenkowski at a Conference on Taxation Dinner (New York, NY), 1988-12-06 (Box 290, Folder 7)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1988-12-08 (Box 290, Folder 8)
  - Arthur L. Carter Hall Dedication (NYU), 1988-12-12 (Box 290, Folder 9)
  - NYU Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1988-12-12 (Box 102, Folder 24)
  - Introduction for Speros Vryonis Lecture on the 900th Anniversary of St. John Monastery (New York, NY), 1988-12-13 (Box 290, Folder 10)
  - Dinner Honoring Mr. and Mrs. Leonard N. Stern (NYU), 1988-12-13 (Box 290, Folder 11)
  - Testimony at a Hearing of the Subcommittee on Education and Health of the Joint Economic Committee (Washington, D.C.), 1988-12-14 (Box 290, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Council Luncheon (NYU), 1988-12-15 (Box 290, Folder 13)
  - Reaction Memo to American Council on Education Document "Issues in the 101st Congress", 1988-12-21 (Box 290, Folder 14)
  - Letter Bidding Farewell to Father Raymond Rafferty (NYU), 1989-01-11 (Box 290, Folder 15)
  - Annual Meeting of the American Council on Education (San Diego, CA), 1989-01-20 (Box 290, Folder 16)
  - Documentation Re: Thomas Eagleton Response to Harold Brown on "Congress and Foreign Policy", 1989-01-20 (Box 290, Folder 17)
  - Medical Center Press Conference Announcing The Tisch Hospital (NYU), 1989-01-25 (Box 290, Folder 18)
  - NYU Alumni Reception in Atlanta (Atlanta, GA), 1989-01-27 (Box 290, Folder 19)
  - Institute of Fine Arts Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-01-30 (Box 102, Folder 25)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies Dinner (NYU), 1989-01-30 (Box 290, Folder 20)
  - Committee of the Year 2000 Meeting (New York, NY), 1989-01-31 (Box 290, Folder 21)
  - Op-Ed Piece -- "An Olive Branch Within Easy Reach", 1989-02 (Box 290, Folder 22)
  - Getty Center for Education in the Arts National Conference (Los Angeles, CA), 1989-02-02 (Box 290, Folder 23)
  - Essay Submission for "Berlin/New York" Project, 1989-02-03 (Box 290, Folder 24)
  - Robert Wood Johnson Press Conference (NYU), 1989-02-06 (Box 290, Folder 25)
  - McGeorge Bundy Book Reception (NYU), 1989-02-06 (Box 290, Folder 26)
  - NYU Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-02-06 (Box 102, Folder 26)
  - Testimony Supplement Statement Re: Student Loan Default Problems, 1989-02-08 (Box 290, Folder 27)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1989-02-09 (Box 290, Folder 28)
  - Brademas Receiving the Hellene of the Year Award at the Athenian Ball (New York, NY), 1989-02-15 (Box 290, Folder 29)
  - Faculty of Arts and Science Board of Overseers Meeting (NYU), 1989-02-16 (Box 290, Folder 30)
  - "Education for a Strong & Sure America," Mid-Atlantic Club Luncheon, 1989-02-16 (Box 291, Folder 1)
  - President's Council Reception (New York, NY), 1989-02-22 (Box 291, Folder 2)
  - Brademas Interview, Broadcast on FNN, 1989-02-22 (Box 291, Folder 3)
  - Essay, "The Challenge of International Education," Published in the Journal of International Affairs, 1989-02-22 (Box 291, Folder 4)
  - United Way and NYU Community Fund Campaign Reception, 2020-01-23 (Box 291, Folder 5)
  - Luncheon Honoring the Comptroller General (NYU), 1989-02-27 (Box 291, Folder 6)
  - NYU Day Events in Albany, 1989-02-28 (Box 291, Folder 7)
  - Metro Center Benefit Luncheon (New York, NY), 1989-03-01 (Box 291, Folder 8)
  - NYC Partnership / Urban Research Center Breakfast (NYU), 1989-03-02 (Box 291, Folder 9)
  - Medical Center Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-03-02 (Box 102, Folder 27)
  - Afternoon at Washington Square, 1989-03-05 (Box 291, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Council Meeting (NYU), 1989-03-08 (Box 291, Folder 11)
  - Comments Preceding the Ramasco Lecture, Department of History (NYU), 1989-03-09 (Box 291, Folder 12)
  - Aphrodisias Colloquium (NYU), 1989-03-09 (Box 291, Folder 13)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1989-03-09 (Box 291, Folder 14)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-03-13 (Box 102, Folder 27)
  - 22nd Annual Real Estate Institute Urban Leadership Award Dinner (New York, NY), 1989-03-15 (Box 291, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Council Luncheon (NYU), 1989-03-23 (Box 291, Folder 16)
  - Association of American Publishers Annual Meeting (Boca Raton, FL), 1989-03-30 (Box 291, Folder 17)
  - Luncheon Commemorating the Enthronement of Archbishop Iakovos (New York, NY), 1989-04-02 (Box 291, Folder 18)
  - Lecture and Dinner Honoring Lee Hamilton (NYU), 1989-04-03 (Box 291, Folder 19)
  - Medical Center Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-04-04 (Box 102, Folder 28)
  - NYU Family Dinner Hosted by David Kriser, 1989-04-05 (Box 291, Folder 20)
  - Presidential Scholars Reception (NYU), 1989-04-08 (Box 291, Folder 21)
  - Annenberg Program Debate, 1989-04-10 (Box 291, Folder 22)
  - Reception to Honor Lewis and Jack Rudin (NYU), 1989-04-11 (Box 291, Folder 23)
  - NYU Alumni Reception (Stamford, CT), 1989-04-12 (Box 291, Folder 24)
  - Reception Honoring Chinua Achebe (NYU), 1989-04-13 (Box 291, Folder 25)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1989-04-13 (Box 291, Folder 26)
  - Conference on "Books, Babies, and Libraries: Making the Connection," New York Public Library (New York, NY), 1989-04-13 (Box 291, Folder 27)
  - Meeting of the Northeastern Association of Graduate Schools (Albany, NY), 1989-04-14 (Box 291, Folder 28)
  - Religion and Public Policy Conference Panel, Georgetown University (Washington, D.C.), 1989-04-14 (Box 291, Folder 29)
  - Law School Revue (NYU), 1989-04-15 (Box 291, Folder 30)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation (NYU), 1989-04-16 (Box 291, Folder 31)
  - Laudatio of the Honorable J. William Fulbright (Athens, Greece), 1989-04-21 and 1989-05 (Box 291, Folder 32)
  - Statement Delivered Before the Subcommittee on Energy & Water Development of the House Committee on Appropriations (Washington, D.C.), 1989-04-21 and 1989-05 (Box 291, Folder 33)
  - Statement Delivered Before the Subcommittee on Natural Resources, Agriculture, Research, & the Environment of the House Committee on Science, Space, and Technology (Washington, D.C.), 1989-04-21 (Box 291, Folder 34)
  - Conference on Abused Children (New York, NY), 1989-04-27 (Box 292, Folder 1)
  - Reception Honoring E.L. Doctorow (NYU), 1989-04-27 (Box 292, Folder 2)
  - NYU Metropolitan Studies Conference on Children (NYU), 1989-04-28 (Box 292, Folder 3)
  - "The Generational Contract: Educating All Our Youngsters for the 1990s," Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching / Americans for Generational Equity Regional Conference, 1989-04-28 (Box 292, Folder 4)
  - Washington Square Arch 100th Anniversary Celebration, 1989-04-30 (Box 292, Folder 5)
  - "Is the Agenda for Science Too Important To Be Left to Scientists?", Nexus Article, May 1989 (Box 292, Folder 6)
  - Advances at NYU, May 1989 (Box 292, Folder 7)
  - Dinner Honoring Robert Maxwell (NYU), 1989-05-01 (Box 292, Folder 8)
  - College of Arts and Science Heads (CASH) Luncheon (NYU), 1989-05-02 (Box 292, Folder 9)
  - Remarks for Dean Harvey Stedmana for Taping of PBS Show, Author, Author, 1989-05-02 (Box 292, Folder 10)
  - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and the Arts Professions Prism Award Luncheon Honoring Robert Maxwell (New York, NY), 1989-05-03 (Box 292, Folder 11)
  - Alumni Council Meeting (NYU), 1989-05-03 (Box 292, Folder 12)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1989-05-04 (Box 292, Folder 13)
  - Greek Press of the Diaspora Dinner (NYU), 1989-05-06 (Box 292, Folder 14)
  - "Some Social Implications of New Technologies," Omni Desk Conference (NYU), 1989-05-08 (Box 292, Folder 15)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-05-08 (Box 102, Folder 29)
  - Institute of Fine Arts Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-05-11 (Box 102, Folder 30)
  - Presentation of the 25-Year Service Awards (NYU), 1989-05-11 (Box 292, Folder 16)
  - NYU Community Fund, 1989-05-16 (Box 292, Folder 17)
  - Trustees Pre-Commencement Dinner (NYU), 1989-05-17 (Box 292, Folder 18)
  - Alumni Commencement Breakfast (NYU), 1989-05-18 (Box 292, Folder 19)
  - Medical Center Commencement (NYU), 1989-05-18 (Box 292, Folder 20)
  - Ceremony Honoring Albert Gallatin Medalist Taggart Whipple (NYU), 1989-05-18 (Box 292, Folder 21)
  - 157th Commencement Exercises (NYU), 1989-05-18 (Box 292, Folder 22)
  - Honorary Degree Citations, 1989-05-18 (Box 292, Folder 23)
  - "Reflections on Congress" at the White Burkett Miller Center of Public Affairs at the University of Virginia, 1989-05-19 (Box 292, Folder 24)
  - Brasenose College Charitable Foundation Dinner (NYU), 1989-05-30 (Box 292, Folder 25)
  - Herbert R. Silverman Scholarship Fund Reception (NYU), 1989-06-01 (Box 292, Folder 26)
  - Wayne E. Hirschkorn Memorial Fund Reception (NYU), 1989-06-06 (Box 292, Folder 27)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-06-05 (Box 102, Folder 31)
  - Medical Center Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-06-06 (Box 102, Folder 32)
  - Breakfast Meeting of the Gallatin Associates & President's Council (NYU), 1989-06-07 (Box 292, Folder 28)
  - Cultural & Educational Agreement Between the U.S. & Spain Reception, United State Information Agency (Washington, D.C.), 1989-06-07 (Box 292, Folder 29)
  - Statement for Press Kit, Archivists Round Table of Metropolitan New York, 1989-06-13 (Box 292, Folder 30)
  - Message to NYU / Yugoslavia Marketing Seminar Message, 1989-06-16 (Box 292, Folder 31)
  - "Higher Education in the 1990s: Prospects & Problems," Gannett Center Conference, 1989-06-18 (Box 292, Folder 32)
  - Medical Center Faculty Meeting (NYU), 1989-06-19 (Box 292, Folder 33)
  - Penthouse Dinner Honoring Pascual Maragall (NYU), 1989-06-21 (Box 292, Folder 34)
  - Article in Oxford Today, 1989-06-23 (Box 292, Folder 35)
  - Silver Shalis Cruise, 1989-06-28 (Box 292, Folder 36)
  - Nomination of Marian Wright Edelman for McGraw-Hill Prize, 1989-06-30 (Box 292, Folder 37)
  - Response to Newsday Editorial, 1989-07-06 (Box 292, Folder 38)
  - Funding for Fairness (NYU), 1989-08-02 (Box 292, Folder 39)
  - Introduction to Medical Center Brochure, 1989-08-22 (Box 292, Folder 40)
  - Undergraduate Convocation, 1989-09-05 (Box 292, Folder 41)
  - New York City Mayoral Candidate Debate Introductions (NYU), 1989-09-06 (Box 292, Folder 42)
  - Op-ed on Drugs, 1989-09-06 (Box 295, Folder 1)
  - Medical Center Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-09-07 (Box 102, Folder 33)
  - Community Service Society Retired Senior Volunteer Program (New York, NY), 1989-09-14 (Box 295, Folder 2)
  - Introduction of Senator Daniel Patrick Moynihan at National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities Leadership Conference, 1990-09-14 (Box 295, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees Executive Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-09-18 (Box 102, Folder 34)
  - Caldwell College 50th Anniversary Convocation (Caldwell, NJ), 1989-09-20 (Box 295, Folder 4)
  - Covenant of Peace Award Dinner, 1989-09-20 (Box 295, Folder 5)
  - Dedication of the Henry Viscardi High School (Albertson, NY), 1989-09-21 (Box 295, Folder 6)
  - Hagop Kevorkian Center Cultural Heritage Conference (NYU), 1989-09-21 (Box 295, Folder 7)
  - World Management Congress, 1989-09-21 (Box 295, Folder 8)
  - Georgetown University President Inaugural Luncheon (Washington, D.C.), 1989-09-23 (Box 295, Folder 9)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration Naming Press Conference, 1989-09-25 (Box 295, Folder 10)
  - Memorial Service for Sidney Hook (NYU), 1989-09-25 (Box 295, Folder 11)
  - Tokyo Broadcasting System Luncheon (NYU), 1989-09-26 (Box 295, Folder 12)
  - Alumni Relations Program Reception (NYU), 1989-09-26 (Box 295, Folder 13)
  - New Graduate Students Reception (NYU), 1989-09-27 (Box 295, Folder 14)
  - Chet Huntley Memorial Lecture, 1989-09-27 (Box 295, Folder 15)
  - International Radio and Television Foundation (IRTF) Benefit Dinner (New York, NY), 1989-09-28 (Box 295, Folder 16)
  - Luncheon Honoring Jorge Semprun (NYU), 1989-09-29 (Box 295, Folder 17)
  - Humanities Council Readings on Greenwich Village, 1989-10-03 (Box 295, Folder 18)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1989-10-05 (Box 295, Folder 19)
  - Events Commemorating President George Vassiliou, 1989-10-05 (Box 295, Folder 20)
  - Medical Center Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-10-10 (Box 102, Folder 35)
  - University Athletics Association Presidents' Press Reception (NYU), 1989-10-11 (Box 295, Folder 21)
  - Alumni Council Meeting, 1989-10-11 (Box 295, Folder 22)
  - New Jersey Regional Alumni Reception (Short Hills, NJ), 1989-10-12 (Box 295, Folder 23)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-10-12 (Box 102, Folder 36)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Luncheon Honoring Soviet Filmmakers (NYU), 1989-10-17 (Box 295, Folder 24)
  - Inaugural Reception for Arthur Imperatore Professorship (NYU), 1989-10-30 (Box 295, Folder 25)
  - Real Estate Institute Campaign Announcement (NYU), 1989-10-31 (Box 295, Folder 26)
  - Dinner Honoring Ralph Marino (NYU), 1989-10-31 (Box 295, Folder 27)
  - Lecture Celebrating the Nancy Hanks Endowment at Duke University (Durham, NC), 1989-11-02 (Box 295, Folder 28)
  - Temple Emanu-El Forum (New York, NY), 1989-11-05 (Box 295, Folder 29)
  - Address at the Donald MacNaughton Symposium, 1989-11-08 (Box 295, Folder 30)
  - All-University Dinner Dance (NYU), 1989-11-08 (Box 295, Folder 31)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1989-11-09 (Box 295, Folder 32)
  - Elmer Holmes Bobst Memorial Room Dedication (NYU), 1989-11-09 (Box 295, Folder 33)
  - United Hellenic American Congress Dinner Dance (Chicago, IL), 1989-11-11 (Box 295, Folder 34)
  - Onassis Center Dedication (NYU), 1989-11-13 (Box 295, Folder 35)
  - Trustees Scholars Reception (NYU), 1989-11-15 (Box 295, Folder 36)
  - Center for Latin American and Caribbean Studies Luncheon (NYU), 1989-11-16 (Box 295, Folder 37)
  - Dinner Honoring Robert F. Wagner (NYU), 1989-11-16 (Box 295, Folder 38)
  - Luncheon Honoring Marie Schwartz, 1989-11-17 (Box 295, Folder 39)
  - Scholarship Foundation of St. Joseph County Meeting (South Bend, IN), 1989-11-19 (Box 295, Folder 40)
  - Lecture by Jose Maria Maravall (NYU), 1989-11-20 (Box 295, Folder 41)
  - Washington Square Park Gift Acknowledgment (NYU), 1989-11-21 (Box 295, Folder 42)
  - Middle States Association of Collegiate Registrars Meeting (Atlantic City, NJ), 1989-11-27 (Box 296, Folder 1)
  - Annual Management Conference of the General Accounting Office (Chantilly, VA), 1989-11-29 (Box 296, Folder 2)
  - Arthur Lehning Tribute Chapter in Voor Arthur Lehning, 1989-12 (Box 296, Folder 3)
  - Medical Center Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-12-05 (Box 297, Folder 1)
  - Dinner Honoring Elie Wiesel (NYU), 1989-12-06 (Box 296, Folder 4)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1989-12-07 (Box 296, Folder 5)
  - Dr. Howard A. Rusk Memorial Service (NYU), 1989-12-07 (Box 296, Folder 6)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1989-12-11 (Box 297, Folder 2)
  - Ed Koch Reception (NYU), 1989-12-11 (Box 296, Folder 7)
  - Education Week Interview, 1989-12-15 (Box 296, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Council Luncheon (NYU), 1989-12-14 (Box 296, Folder 9)